inksoft.com 2010-10-08

# Privacy

Privacy Policy:

InkSoft is committed to respecting the privacy rights of our customers and all visitors to our website. We have instituted the following policies and procedures to ensure that your privacy is respected. By visiting InkSoft you agree to the policies stated below.

What information InkSoft collects:

InkSoft collects e-mail addresses of people who send us e-mail, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, user-specific information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as name and address, telephone number, payment information (e.g., credit card number and billing address). We are not allowed to disclose such personal information without your written permission.

What InkSoft does with this information:

The information InkSoft collects is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our website, used to notify consumers about updates to our website or used by us to contact consumers for marketing purposes. From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If you supply us with your postal address on-line you will only receive the information for which you provided us your address. Customers may prevent their information from being used for purposes other than those for which it was originally collected by e-mailing us at the address listed below.

Sharing information with outside parties:

InkSoft does not share, rent or sell the information you provide us with any other organizations. With respect to Ad Servers, we do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies.

How InkSoft safeguards your personal information:

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information, such as credit card number, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. We attempt to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. No method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Disclosure:

InkSoft may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

Disclosure:

InkSoft may disclose personally identifiable information under special circumstances, such as to comply with court orders requiring us to do so or when your actions violate the Terms of Service.

Client Data Storage:

InkSoft owns the data storage, databases and all rights to the InkSoft application. However, we make no claim to the rights of your data. You retain all rights to your data and we will never contact your clients directly, or use your data for our own business advantage or to compete with you or market to your clients.

Changes to this Privacy Policy:

InkSoft reserves the right to modify this privacy statement at any time. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here or by means of a notice on our homepage so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

Questions:

For any questions or comments about the InkSoft privacy policy, please contact us at:

5203 Juan Tabo NE  
Sutie 2-E   
Albuquerque, NM 87111

We can be reached via e-mail at info@inksoft.com
